vicman.net 2019-08-27

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Statement (вЂњPrivacy PolicyвЂќ, вЂњPolicyвЂќ, вЂњStatementвЂќ) describes the policies and practices of the VicMan company (вЂњVIcManвЂќ), in terms of collecting, using, and safeguarding the private information that may be obtained through use of the company's products, services and website. This Privacy Policy applies to each of the VicMan entities, but not to VicMan's partners or affiliates, which may have independent privacy policies. Questions about this Statement may be submitted through вЂContact usвЂ™ form. 

## Information Collection

Personal information is collected from customers only after obtaining consent, which is acquired when customers are prompted for information when subscribing to the services, downloading a product, or requesting information from the company. Personally-identifiable information is not collected when a user simply browses the website. 

## Disclosure of Information

Please rest assured that VicMan does not provide the obtained information to third parties and takes all reasonable measures to guarantee the safety and security of the user information. You need to acknowledge, however, that, although VicMan does its best to protect your personal data, the company cannot pledge its absolute safety. The reason for it is that whenever you publicly disclose information on the company's website (e.g. leave comments or reviews), that information can easily be seen, collected or used by any other unauthorized people. 

## Product Download

Downloading a product will often require the customer to provide personal information. This information will be used by VicMan to contact the customer, provide news about VicMan, its products and services, including product updates and associated promotional material. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a computer's hard disk containing information about the owner. VicMan does not employ the use and does not exercise any access or control of cookies. 

## External Links

The VicMan website contains links to external websites which are outside the scope of this Privacy Statement. VicMan is not responsible for the privacy practices of the other sites and does not control the accuracy of information displayed by such websites. 

## How to contact us

If you have questions regarding the Policy, please contact us via the form on the site, and we will endeavor to respond to your request. 

## Amendments

VicMan reserves the right to amend this privacy statement at any time. Any amendment will be made by posting the changes to the website. Customers must check the website periodically to be aware of any changes to the Privacy Statement. Your continued use of the website or VicMan product or service constitutes your acceptance of those changes. 

Last Updated: March 12, 2015
